Finding Aid for Grandville-Jenison Congregational Church (Grandville, Mich.) records, 1838-1936
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Grandville-Jenison Congregational Church (Grandville, Mich.) records 1838-1936
Grandville-Jenison Congregational Church (Grandville, Mich.)
1 microfilm roll
86756 mf 634c
Church formed from merger of First Congregational Church, Grandville, and Jenison Congregational Church; church records.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group was deposited by church through Rev. Walter M. Swann (donor no. 666 ) in 1939.
Periodic additions to the records are not expected.
The record group is open to research.
The originals were returned to the donor in 2012. The library has only the microfilm copy.
The Grandville-Jenison Congregational Church was formed by the merger of the First Congregational Church of Grandville and the Jenison Congregational Church.
The record group includes records of the individual churches. Records of the First Congregational Church of Grandville include minutes and membership lists, 1838-1934, minutes of the Congregational Society, 1863-1891, and of the Sunday School, 1868-1885 and 1908. Records of the Jenison Congregational Church include minutes and membership records, 1903-1936. Other records include articles of association, historical notes, and miscellaneous correspondence, notices, and receipts.
Subjects:
Congregational Churches--Michigan--Grandville.; Congregational Churches--Michigan--Jenison.; Grandville (Mich.); Jenison (Mich.); Grandville-Jenison Congregational Church (Grandville, Mich.); First Congregational Church (Grandville, Mich.); Jenison Congregational Church (Jenison, Mich.)
- First Congregational Church, Grandville
  - Minutes and membership lists
    - 1838-1869 (Reel 1)
    - 1868-1907 (Reel 1)
    - 1907-1916 (Reel 1)
    - 1917-1934 (Reel 1)
  - Minutes of Congregational Society, 1863-1891 (Reel 1)
  - Sunday School minutes, membership lists, accounts
    - 1868-1885 (Reel 1)
    - 1908 (Reel 1)
- Jenison Congregational Church
  - Minutes and membership lists
    - 1903-1924 (Reel 1)
    - 1923-1936 (Reel 1)
- Other records
  - Articles of association; incorporation materials (Reel 1)
  - Historical notes (Reel 1)
  - Miscellaneous (correspondence, notices, receipts, etc.) (Reel 1)